http://www.actionpistol.org/privacy

Action pistol.orgAction pistol.orgAction pistol.orgAction pistol.orgAction pistol.orgAction pistol.orgAction pistol.orgAction pistol.orgHomeGet StartedFormatsStart HereGearOrientationCalendarNorCal USPSABy RegionAlmaden ValleyCAPSLEl Dorado EDPSLivermore-PleasantonNCPSNorth Coast Pistol LeagueNorth Valley ShootersRichmond HotshotsShasta ShootersSons of Action PistolSolano TargetMastersTehama ShootersOther ClubsCENCAL USPSA SectionSouthern California ClubsCowboy Action SASSLincoln Rifle ClubMotherlode Gun ClubNorCal Precision RifleSacramento IDPASacramento Valley SteelWestern Nevada Pistol411AboutSponsorsContactPrivacyMoreHomeGet StartedFormatsStart HereGearOrientationCalendarNorCal USPSABy RegionAlmaden ValleyCAPSLEl Dorado EDPSLivermore-PleasantonNCPSNorth Coast Pistol LeagueNorth Valley ShootersRichmond HotshotsShasta ShootersSons of Action PistolSolano TargetMastersTehama ShootersOther ClubsCENCAL USPSA SectionSouthern California ClubsCowboy Action SASSLincoln Rifle ClubMotherlode Gun ClubNorCal Precision RifleSacramento IDPASacramento Valley SteelWestern Nevada Pistol411AboutSponsorsContactPrivacyHomeGet StartedCalendarNorCal USPSAOther Clubs411
Privacy PolicyThis privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for ActionPistol.org (“Website”) and applies solely herein.INFORMATION COLLECTION,USE, AND SHARINGWe are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via the Website, email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.Your information will be used to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us, or by the club you contact using their form shown on their page. Information you provide us for the purposes of completing any Website forms is directly inserted into your documents without legal interpretation, a decision tree, or if/then analysis. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. register for an event. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or events, or changes to this privacy policy.YOUR ACCESS TO AND CONTROL OF INFORMATIONYou may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via email or phone number provided on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
SECURITYWe take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information (if applicable) via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.This Website will not request sensitive information (i.e. credit card) for any reason.LINKED SITESThis web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.UPDATESOur Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.We will never, ever collect or disclose information about you or your firearms.  If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately at jldunlap@2dunlap.com.
© 2020 Actionpistol.org - All Rights Reserved.Designed by Fritz Chin FFL.com
